

Graphic Designer and Web Designer

Hi, I'm Olivia! I am a junior at Parsons School of Design studying a BFA in Communication Design. I specialize in graphic design, branding, website design, and illustration. I'm interested in creating unique experiences through design and interaction.

oliviahu26@gmail.com

Manhattan, New York

www.imoliviahu.com

(imoliviahu

### **SKILLS**

**InDesign** Creative Illustrator Organized **After Effects** Collaboration **Photoshop Typography Premiere Pro Website Design Figma Motion Graphics** Social Media **Branding HTML & CSS** Illustration **Google Suite Photography** 

## **EDUCATION**

Parsons School of Design, The New School

Communication Design BFA (GPA: 3.9)

CS50: Introduction to Computer Science

Harvard edX Online Course

August 2020-present

June 2020-August 2020

Sharron Art Center June 2020–August 2020
Refined my fundamental art skills through sketching, painting, and sculpture.

# LANGUAGES

English
Chinese
Spanish
•••••••
••••••

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Yeh IDeology | Graphic Designer May 2022-Present

Developed brand system by creating layout, information structure, animations, typography, and colors of Yeh IDeology's Thrive By Design website.

Created and executed promotional motion graphics and writing for monthly newsletters. Assisted in designing covers for Yeh IDeology's Designing Futures Podcast.

# Youth and Sustainability | Brand Designer

Embolden Jewelry | Brand & Social Media

March 2022-April 2022

June 2020-August 2022

Designed brand system by creating logo, colors, and typography for Youth & Sustainability. Coded and designed the mobile version of website while collaborating with a team to develop brand content and structure of website.

### **INTERESTS**











Digital Art

Created branding system for Embolden Jewelry by designing logo, layout, structure, colors, images, and typography, and promotional graphics for website. Photographed jewelry and developed profile feed for business's Instagram.

#### Starbucks | Barista

June 2021-August 2021

Memorized and crafted beverages in a fast-paced working environment while communicating with coworkers and customers to facilitate the best experience.





**Comics** 

#### **AWARDS**

National Medal from Scholastic Art and Writing Awards 2020 High Merit Student Award from Celebrating Art Contest 2019 & 2020